Hello friends, right now we will discuss three steps -
Larsen & Toubro,
ICICI Lombard and ESI. The results of Larsen &
Toubro and ESI are going to come soon
and the results of ICICI Lombard will come a
little while ago, so like that too
and through that we will see what should happen. So
friends, before we start, I
want to tell you that for internet,
please subscribe to our channel. Here
we provide for advance interest rates. You
can subscribe
on this link.
I want you to keep in mind that whatever
investment you make,
please do comment from your financial advisor.
Our videos are for additional purposes. So
friends, now we were to
look at ICICI Lombard PIMS. Jio's
net profit is that of the patient which is seven four,
okay,
and we will look into it a little more in
detail. I had already told you about
its profit, its big, its GDPI
is 9.00, with return on equity
earlier it is 63.72. Their
solvency ratio has also improved.
2.0 2.0 76 and
I believe this youth has been his, so
we should not use it, friends, I have placed
this here and here 13 subscribe and
if subscribe subscribe
MP3 will have to keep a stop loss of 1320 and it
is the first one that will be accepted because
it has crossed 12 times the very strong resistance,
then do not forget to subscribe subscribe
friends, I will subscribe you can
stop and our skirt can be
and you have so
friends, this was my analysis
of ICICI Lombard, now we had to
look at one thing, so people say it is a
mess
and we will see what is in its results,
so their stomach, that person will do
19, 23.70 body,
this is the estimated net profit, they are
suitable candidates, but you should keep in mind that
near basic it will increase, but on
quarterly basis it
is expected to go down in a manner, Yuvi is not subscribed,
remind me sports have improved
Ambuja Cement is also not very
excited, good results are
not expected if we look at it at the quarterly level
and in the recent past, the AISI team has told about its new
dry capacity products,
which is a unique A1 grade unit
of America, friends are
liking it very much, do it very well 12 times
and subscribe, should you buy it,
subscribe it 18 times and
subscribe because subscribe it will be
clear to you
that the rest because it is following the deadline so well
and the moving average also, so
I will not look at any other indicator in the stock, there is
no need to do it forcefully,
so friends, this topic will be
very good for you, if you like it then consider
yourself lucky, subscribe,
subscribe,
this was my study, friends, bring it to AISI,
now if we look at the news of LNT, it has been
told about the dividend entry as per the investors whether it is
good or not, then those middle aged people, but it is a
very regular dividend,  Look here,
if you understand that according to what this company does, the
facility and procedure of IMD first 29 on cents is synonymous with the
growth of the company is increasing, so does the
incident have milk potential or not, so
their share has fallen a bit,
but will their dividend fall or not,
so the confusion is that you
can buy and subscribe to the dividend,
that these securities have made a little estimate for this,
so here it will
see the net profit, then the scheme will show the village and
23.1 Chairman Mirwaiz, but if all this is applied then
it will reduce a little there
and so we will know what were the
specifications, everyone knows that
if you are appointed on the solar power station, you
can subscribe, subscribe, and here this subscription,
which seems fine to me with our contributory pension,
so I will quickly write down the duty Takiya Gomez, so
friends, you can see the system, the increase in
Chittorgarh Tera is around 20%
Hey crackers friends, what we will take in this will be
between 15070 to sixteen, so
this is trading strategies
and anti, so
friends, I hope you liked the video, please
like and subscribe to us,
that will keep our motivation going, so that
you can follow us on Telegram, Twitter, Facebook,
so our page is in the name of trading,
whatever development is in your mind,
friends, you can write in the comment section, we
will reply to it in due time, thank you friends,
show more